Someone needs to scout ahead.
Taking this guy out
first is our best option.
They're more than up
for this little mission.
Just leave it to us!
Masa, he's already on the radio!
Damn this prick!
I can't let him escape
now, especially here.
I'm trying to breathe, but I
don't want to give it to you.
I'm trying to find out this way,
I'm trying to change the world.
Guido Mista's outlook on life has
always been summarized by the saying,
simple is best.
He found joy in the banality
of sleep, the sway of branches,
the smooth creeping of clouds, the
aroma of wine, the texture of formaggio.
He would flirt with a beautiful
girl despite her disapproval.
If he needed money, he'd
wait outside the theater?
For some poor soul to
slander the featured actor!
and beat them for every
last lira they had.
But sometimes the beatdown befell him,
stopping only with police intervention.
It had its ups and downs, but Mista
considered his life a happy one.
Some might have called
this foolish naivete
but in the mind of Mista
it was simple calculus.
Overanalyzing was the bedfellow of fear
and fear wasn't part of the equation.
But soon after Mista
turned 17 something changed
his view on life he came to the conclusion
that The destiny of every
soul is set in youth
one may feel helplessly
stuck that nothing feels?
straightforward or easy,
but in the end we all travel down
the path we are supposed to take.
It was a clear summer's night and
Mista was on his usual passeggiata.
Hey Mista! Hey!
You ladies want to party tonight?
Sorry doll, but we got other plans.
Ciao! See ya!
No!
Let go of me!
Now why would I do that you little slut!
Looking in he could see
a nearly nude woman being
assaulted blood was gushing
from her nose and mouth.
And she was nearly unconscious the urge
to not get involved was strong yet.
His instincts had taken over causing
his body to spring into action.
Even if a shooter fired within close
proximity it wouldn't guarantee a hit.
In a state of panic and momentary fear,
the shooter could easily fire the gun
without having acquired proper aim.
The aggressor let out two shots.
Both bullets grazed Misa's arm
before fading into the darkness.
What?
Get away from me, you freaking weirdo!
Three, four, five, six.
Each bullet was somehow
swallowed up in the darkness.
His accomplices frantically fired, but
in what can only be called a miracle,
not a single bullet struck Mista.
Mista was surprised by his ability to
keep calm in this torrent of bullets.
What the hell?
Who is this guy? Bro!
Mista grabbed a gun
along with some bullets,
and despite the volley heading his
way, Cooley loaded the chambers.
Like a nurse sliding the
syringe into a bulging vein,
he pulled the trigger
calmly and deliberately.
He took aim and fired four perfect shots.
He'd never taken another
man's life before that night,
yet he felt no hesitation or regret.
In a moment of hopelessness,
Mista found the strength to cut through
the darkness that gripped his soul.
Die!
It looks like the driver is
the real owner of the truck.
I couldn't tell before, but
his right leg isn't injured.
I wasn't going to off you, but now.
Dammit, that hurts!
Screw you!
That's twice now you shot
me, you gun-toting psycho!
Quit squirming!
Next time, I'll be sure
to take better aim.
Jeez, what kind of lame-ass line was that?
What I should have said is, how
are you not a pile of sausage meat?
I shot your ugly mug square on.
Is it possible that the bullet
just missed his brain somehow?
You know, Mista, that last-ish
effort of yours was quite endearing.
I mean, Mista is your name, isn't it?
Help me out with something.
It seems even your friends are on this
beautiful island enjoying the sights.
But only you have gazed upon my visage.
Isn't that right?
You fooled me with that radio booby trap.
And you even nailed me
with two cheap shots.
But now that we're face to face, and
I'm armed with my sand arts and crafts,
I can knock down any bullet fired from that
ridiculous peashooter you point around.
By the way, I can't say I was
paying attention back there.
How many bullets did
you fire off? Let's see.
I'm fairly certain you
fired four on this truck.
And you shot off two
back at that dumpy shack.
What'd you think?
I did a good job counting, huh, mi-star?
Now I can get in nice
and close and beat the
shit out of you without
a care in the world.
Right?
Shit, he's right. I gotta reload.
What the hell is up with my hand? Damn it.
It's like it's stuck to this thing.
Hey, idiot.
Why are you still driving?
Hit the brakes, dumbass.
Believe me, I wanna, but I
need some help over here.
Seriously, kid, you gotta help me.
It's out of control.
Ponder it for a sec.
Why do you think I'd go to the trouble
of telling you that you were out of ammo?
Out of the goodness of my heart?
No, Mista.
It was because I knew you'd crash and
burn with this truck, so why hide it?
Your driver can't take his foot off the
gas, and his hands aren't going anywhere.
I'm only telling you all
this because I know full well
you can't reload with your
hand fixed to the truck.
Those are the bullets that
Bastardo's stand deflected.
They're frozen in mid-air,
like in suspended animation,
moving in tandem with the truck.
So that's his game.
He must have immobilized
the bullets with his power.
That's how he cemented me
and the driver to this truck.
His ability lets him freeze objects
in the exact place he touches them.
That's why my bullet never made
it past the skin on his forehead.
Of course a surface wound
wouldn't finish him off.
You know, Mista,
if I'm honest, I couldn't be happier
that you decided to take off after me.
I'm so happy, in fact, that I'm willing to
forgive this little scratch you gave me.
After all,
till now, no one knew for sure whether
Popo's great treasure even existed.
It's always been a desperate rumor.
But the ferocity with which you're
trying to kill me proves it exists!
You, friend, just reignited my hopes
and gave me a brand new reason to live!
I'm gonna save her every
single moment of swiping
that sweet lira from
that creature Bucciarati!
I already told you I can knock away your
petty bullets like the
annoyance as they are!
What, there was another
bullet in the shadows?
So, Mr.
Stand allows him to fire two
bullets in a single shot.
But, I still have a
chance to work my magic!
Oh yeah!
Way to go!
I don't know what I'd do without
you guys, number six and seven.
Now that your fuckly ass is out of the
way, our worries just became roadkill.
I let that bullet-brained
asshole get me again!
I swear, he'll die for this.
That 10 billion lira is going to be mine!
There has to be a way to beat
him, but it won't be easy.
This guy's a tough one.
Time to dig deep.
Blood.
A vehicle.
Mista and the enemy must be in some
kind of car, heading to higher ground.
Would I even be able to
make it there in time?
No, I can't do that.
I just have to find them.
Four bullets?
What the unholy hell is going on?
How can I only have four bullets?
This doesn't make a
lick of freaking sense.
What happened?
Really, Mista?
It's because you dropped one.
Yeah, you dropped the other bullet.
Well, you of all people should
know the number four is bad news.
You can't load four bullets into the gun.
It won't end well.
My hands are finally free.
My feet are too.
I can stop this thing.
No way, Bob.
Huh?
But a little while ago, you were
screaming at me to stop the truck.
Well, I changed my mind, so deal with it.
Now be a good driver and listen.
I need you to take me
to Marina Grande. Hurry.
I've got a friend waiting for me.
There must be another
way for us to get there.
Look, I promise I'm not going to hurt you.
I'll even make it up to you later. Got it?
My bullets only go skin
deep with this bastard.
I can't inflict any major damage.
He can also fix things in place,
making this an uphill battle.
If I could just get a bullet in his mouth,
he couldn't defend himself from there.
It might actually kill him.
But I only have four bullets left.
I just had to get stuck with that number.
Three would have been way better.
I know what he looks like
and how he fights now.
I should book it.
I'll head back to the harbor
and reconvene with Giorno.
I have a bunch of extra
ammo back there, too.
That bastard!
What the hell?
When did he climb up the cliff?
Stop the truck! Huh?
What are you talking about?
I said stop the damn truck!
Now get to it!
It's a maniac again!
Well, Miesta,
if you thought I'd just let
you tell your friends about me,
then you're an even bigger
lummox than I took you for!
Struggle all you like!
You're never getting away from me!
So, he can hold rocks in the air
just like he did the bullets, huh?
He must have used them like
a ladder to get up here.
Why the hell did you
stop the truck, you ass?
Get moving!
You need to step on it now!
If you so much as slow down, you're dead!
If this is how you want to settle
things, then come and get some!
Hey, dick noodle!
Drive this truck like
your life depends on it!
A few light taps will do the trick.
You'd be surprised what a
little steady tapping can do.
Power tends to accumulate
at the point of fixation.
It's best not to strike at full tilt.
Proper aim becomes
unattainable and projects
the vector of one's
projectile to the opponent.
And then, the release!
What?
It came right back to you, Mista.
I saw your bullets fly out of control.
Those little stands of
yours are a bit unruly.
It doesn't take a lot.
All you need are a few taps and a
tiny bit of force to get the job done.
It's very much like
entering SOS in Morse code.
The aim's not perfect, and it's not great
on things that can't seem to stay still.
But we've finally reached the
perfect moment to end your existence.
Of course I'm in this mess.
My luck is totally shot.
Four has never been a good number,
Even as a kid, I knew that.
You never know what you're gonna
get when it shows its ugly face.
Thankfully, the other numbers
are there to pick up the slack.
I've got one shot left, which must
mean the worst is behind me, right?
Lucky number one, don't fail me now!
Number five, number six,
let's do the damn thing!
Together, we can end this prick!
This is our last shot, boys,
so we have to make it count!
Yeah!
You can drop the pathetic
bravado act, Mista.
Your trigger-happy days are over, moron.
I don't care what your
bullet-riding stooges
can do or how many of
them you shoot at me.
At this distance, I can do
whatever the hell I want.
I can protect myself
and have time to spare.
Come on, you should know by now that it's
utterly impossible to best me, right?
Yo, loudmouth!
If I said I had one bullet left in
this chamber, would you believe me?
That's right, you heard me.
I've still got one shot left.
If I shoot this off and you
manage to knock it away,
then I'll be out of bullets
and completely at your mercy.
You'll find out sooner or
later, so I lie to you.
If I screw up this last
shot, you'd know anyway.
I'm out of ammo after this, so I thought
you'd appreciate my being up front.
But honestly, whether or not I botch
this play is still up in the air.
Although, if we're being real with
ourselves, we both know you're gonna die.
Why do you insist on
spewing nonsense, Mista?
Prattle on about your
silly bullets all you want.
It doesn't really matter.
You can shoot one or a
hundred of those at me,
but you're never gonna
be able to bring me down.
Oh, it wasn't nonsense.
You'll drop your guard soon enough,
there's no question about it.
Especially since you know
I only have one shot left.
You're full of it, you know that.
Get ready, he's gonna use his stand!
Leave it to me!
Now here we go!
We got one target!
So put your backs into it!
You're aiming for the inside
of my mouth, aren't you?
He just opened his mouth for us!
You know what they say about gift horses!
Sure do!
Suit him in the kisser!
I knew it.
Damn, that hurts a lot.
I knew that's exactly where
you were going to aim.
It was obvious.
It's common sense to aim for the mouth.
My powered anchor objects would
be rendered useless inside there.
Fending off your attack would suck.
So I thought I'd open my
mouth for you instead.
What the hell?
Now the guy can even stop
bullets with his mouth?
Give me a break!
Urgh, shit.
This hurts more than I expected.
Sil, I guess you were telling the truth
when you said that would be your last shot.
You don't seem so eager to shoot now.
What happened to that Kinoto spirit?
If that's all you got, then allow me to
show off the firepower on this beauty.
It's finally ready for launch, Mista!
Now bombs away!
Suck on this, and die!
Mista's plan really worked!
He knew it was out of ammo
and let his guard down!
It's just like they always
say, the closer the better!
And when we're at point-blank range,
our aim is even better than before!
Wait, what?
But how?
When could they have... Shit!
They're too close!
Give it to all, fellas! Aim... and...
Artsy Crafts! Guard up!
He split it in two?
I know I could take another
direct hit, but there's no way.
He couldn't be aiming for that, could he?
No, I'm just imagining it.
Tell me he isn't really shooting for that!
His target!
I aimed at the bullet hole from before.
Hitting the previous bullet head on
forced it deeper inside your skull.
And now it's on a one-way
collision course with your brain.
Good luck anchoring that, dopey dick.
But like I said, I'm out of bullets.
So if it doesn't kill you, I'm screwed.
We did it!
Yeah!
Nice!
Would you give it a rest
already, number three?
How many times have I told you
to stop badgering number five?
Man, he's still hanging on, with
a bullet to the brain no less.
I guess your stand really is invincible.
I know Bucciarati told me
not to kill you, but...
We're going back!
Now take me back to the Harbor.
What is wrong with you?
And what were you two doing up there?
I'm so confused!
Dumbass shits!
What do they take me for?
Stop the truck, driver!
Step on it, driver!
This ain't some taxi, stronzo!
You assholes don't scare me.
I let you off easy, but if I ever
see you again, you're gonna pay
Sorry to intrude, but we have to move it.
I'm after someone and need you to take
me to the top of the island right now
But I'll just sit there we have to go
you are planning to help me, right?
Let's go.
Every time I close my eyes.
Wake up feeling so horny.
I can't get you out of my mind.
Since you'll be all I see.
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me.
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need.
Tonight I need your mind.
I need your mind.
Tonight you got my time.
Yeah, you won't give it, baby.
Tonight you won't be sorry.
Tonight you got my mind.
You got my mind, all I
want to do is free you.
What must I say, what must I do,
to show how much I'm going to free you?
I'm going to break you.
Thank you.